Knight to queen's bishop-five.
马跳C3
Oh,very nice. What's
Leonard going to do?
哦 很好 Leonard该怎么做呢?
Does he give up the pawn or
does he give up the position?
他是放弃卒 还是放弃位置?
Let's find out. Leonard,ready?
咱拭目以待吧 Leonard 准备好了?
Ready.
好了
Go.
开始
Damn it. I slipped.
该死 我滑了一下
Too bad. You know the rules of
Secret Agent Laser Obstacle Chess.
可惜啊 你也知道激光障碍
象棋特工的游戏规则
Leonard died again,Sheldon. You're up.
Leonard又死了 Sheldon 该你了
Despite my deep love of chess,lasers
and aerosol disinfectant,I must forfeit.
虽然我深爱象棋 激光和喷雾剂
但我必须放弃游戏
Why?
为啥啊?
- Because it's almost 11:00.
- So?
- 因为已经快11点了
- 所以呢?
So,Penny has a "don't knock on my door before
11:00 or I punch you in the throat" rule.
Penny定了个"11点前别敲我家门
否则我一拳把你打成哑巴"的规矩
Hey,you know what'd be a great idea?
嘿 我想到一个绝妙的点子
We get some girls over here and
play Laser Optical Strip Chess.
咱找几个姑娘来玩激光障碍脱衣象棋
Believe me,Howard,any girl who would be willing
to play that,you don't want to see naked.
信我一句 Howard 凡是愿意来玩的
你都不忍心看她们脱光
You underestimate me.
你小看我
Penny. Penny. Penny.
Penny Penny Penny
Hey,Sheldon.
嘿 Sheldon
- It's 11:00 a.m.
- I know. You're safe.
- 11点了哦
- 我知道 你很安全
This package came
while you were at work.
这包裹是你上班时寄来的
Oh,great,my rhinestones. Thank you.
太好了 我的莱茵仿钻 谢谢
- Excuse me.
- What?
- 等下
- 干嘛?
- You have to sign this.
- What is it?
- 你得签这个
- 啥东西?
When I signed for the package,I was
deputized by the United Parcel Service
我签收这个包裹时
即代表联合邮递公司
and entrusted with its final delivery.
受委托将其转交给你
I now need you to acknowledge receipt of the package
so that I'm fully indemnified and no longer liable.
现在需要你确认收到包裹
说明我安全送达不再负任何责任
Sheldon,it's just a box of rhinestones.
Sheldon 只不过是一盒子莱茵石嘛
Well,the contents are irrelevant.
A legal bailment has been created.
内容不重要 主要是确立合法托管关系
Does that mean nothing to you?
你满不在乎是吧?
It means nothing to anybody.
谁在乎这些啊
Come here,let me show
you what I'm doing.
进来 看看我在干嘛
Bailment describes a
relationship in common law
托管是法律中的一种关系
where a physical possession of
personal property,or "chattels,"
即对私有财产 或者说"动产"的所有权
is transferred from one person,the
bailor,to another person,the bailee...
从一人 即委托人转给另一人 受托者...
ah,yeah,yeah. Look,look,look!
I started a business.
好了 好了 瞧啊瞧 我做生意了
Obviously,not a cleaning business.
显然不是做清洁工作的
No,I'm making flower barrettes. See?
不是 我在做小花发夹 瞧见没
I call them Penny Blossoms.
我叫它们"Penny小花"
I made one for myself,then all
the girls at work wanted one.
我给自己做了一个
结果上班那的女孩们都要
Then I showed some to this lady
who runs a shop in Old Town.
后来我给奥德城一开铺子的女士看了
She sells cards and homemade jewelry.
She said she wanted to sell them.
她是卖卡片和自制首饰的
她说要卖我的发夹
I said,"Okay." And in
one week,I made a $156.
我说"好哇" 一周我就赚了156美刀
Good for you. Sign here.
真不错 签字
Sheldon,don't you get it?
Sheldon 还不明白吗?
If this takes off,I won't
have to be a waitress anymore.
如果这事有起色
我再也不用做服务生了
But then who will bring me my
cheeseburger on Tuesday nights?
那每周二晚谁给我拿芝士汉堡啊?
- Another waitress.
- What's her name?
- 别的服务生咯
- 叫什么名字?
I don't know.
不知道呢
And you're going to
let her handle my food?
不知道就让她给我送餐?
Nancy. Her name is Nancy.
Nancy 她叫Nancy
I think you're just making that up.
我看你是瞎编的吧
Sheldon,I'm sorry about
your hamburger,okay?
Sheldon 汉堡的事抱歉了 好吗?
I just don't want to be a
waitress for the rest of my life.
我真是不想做一辈子服务生
Cheeseburger. I get a cheeseburger.
是芝士汉堡 我要的是芝士汉堡
Fine,cheeseburger.
好了啦 芝士汉堡
Maybe I'd be better off with Nancy.
或许Nancy能招待的更好一点
So,what do you think? I mean,this
could be a business,right?
你觉得咋样? 能成一番事业吧?
How many of these can you make a day?
这玩意你一天能做多少个?
About 20.
20来个
And how much profit do you
make per... Penny Blossom?
你一个"Penny小花"能挣多少...钱?
I don't know,like,50
cents. I'm not sure.
不知道 5毛钱吧 说不好
Of course you're not. All right...
当然了 好吧...
Ten dollars a day times five days a
week times 52 weeks a year is $2,600.
一天10块钱 每周5天 每年52周
那你能挣2600块
- That's all?
- Before taxes.
- 就这么点儿?
- 税前
I don't have to pay taxes on this stuff.
这玩意还交什么税啊
I believe the Internal Revenue
Service would strongly disagree.
国内税收署肯定会强烈反对
But,if you took advantage of modn marketing
techniques,and you optimized your manufacturing process,
但是 如果你利用现代销售技术
完善制作工艺
you might be able to make
this a viable business.
说不定这生意能做成
And you know about that stuff?
你对那些都懂不?
Penny...
I'm a physicist.
我是物理学家
I have a working knowledge of the entire
universe and everything it contains.
我对整个宇宙及其
包含的事物都有所了解
Who's Radiohead?
Radiohead是干嘛的?
I have a working knowledge of the
important things in the universe. Good luck.
我对整个宇宙及其包含的
重要事物都有所了解 祝你好运了
Sheldon,hold on.
Sheldon 等下
Could you maybe show me how
to make more money with this?
能不能教我怎么用这些赚更多钱?
- Of course I could.
- Sheldon,wait!
- 等然能了
- Sheldon 等等!
Will you?
行吗?
Just to be clear here,you're
asking for my assistance.
咱说清楚 你是请求我帮忙
Yes.
是的
And you understand that will
involve me telling you what to do?
你清楚期间我会指导你去做事?
I understand.
我清楚
And you're not allowed to be sarcastic
or snide to me while I'm doing so.
我要你做事时 你不许冷嘲热讽
Okay.
好吧
Good.
很好
Let's begin with the premise that everything
you've done up to this point is wrong.
咱先前提假设你目前
做的一切都是错的
Oh,imagine that.
哦 可不是嘛
- Sarcasm. Good-bye.
- No,sorry. Wait!
- 挖苦 别了
- 别走 对不起 等等!
Please come back!
快回来嘛!
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
-=伊甸园美剧http://sfile.ydy.com=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
sync:咔肉肉
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: penny thera
校对: penny
时间轴: 咔肉肉
双语:徐小帆
The Big Bang
Theory Season02 Episode18
天才理论传
第二季 第18集
There. Done.
好了 做好了
All right. 12 minutes and 17 seconds.
看看 12分17秒
Pretty good,right?
还不错哈?
That's 4. 9 Penny Blossoms per hour.
也就是一小时做4.9个"Penny小花"
Based on your cost of materials
and your wholesale selling price,
根据你的材料钱和批发价
you'll effectively be paying
yourself... $5.19 a day.
你一天实际能挣5.19块美元
A day?
一天?
There are children in a sneaker
factory in Indonesia who outearn you.
印尼运动鞋厂的小孩都比你赚的多
That just can't be right.
不对啊
- You're questioning my math?
- No,sorry.
- 你质疑我的算数?
- 没有 抱歉
- Want me to show my work?
- Oh,God,no.
- 用我给你演示遍怎么算的吗?
- 哦 天啊 可别
- Just please tell me what to do about it.
- All right.
- 就告诉我该怎么办吧
- 好的
Are you familiar with the development
that resulted from Honor\ Blanc's
你了解Honore Blanc1778年
使用可替换零件
1778 use of interchangeable parts?
给工业带来什么发展吗?
The assembly line,of course.
不就是装配线嘛
Okay,you know what,if I'm not allowed to be
snide,you're not allowed to be condescending.
好了 这样吧 既然你不让我讽刺
那你也不许表现得高人一等
That wasn't a part of our original
agreement,and I don't agree to it now.
最初的协定里可没有这条
我现在也不同意
All right,fine. How are we supposed to set up
machines and conveyor belts in my apartment?
随便了 那我们怎么在我公寓
弄机器和传送带啊?
You're thinking of the moving assembly line,an
understandable but not excusable mistake.
你说的是流动装配线啊
可以理解但无法原谅的错误
No. The...
不是的 流动...
The moving assembly line,that was
introduced by Henry Ford in 1908.
流动装配线是由亨利・福特
在1908年引进的
That innovation is what made
possible our modern consumer culture
是这项革新技术通过低费用生产
by enabling a low-unit
cost for manufactured goods.
促成了现代消费文化
I guess that isn't one of the
topics discussed on your Radiohead.
我看Radiohead不讲这些东西吧
Let's go. We're going to
miss the coming attractions.
走了 别错过精彩的事
What's the matter?
怎么了?
I think I bruised a testicle
capturing that last pawn.
我想我吃上一个卒时挫伤了睾丸
* Please pay attentn and listen to me*
* Please pay attention and listen to me*
* Give me some time
to blow the man down *
* Give me some time to blow the man down *
* I'm a deepwater sailor
just come from Hong Kong *
* Give me way,hey,blow the man down *
* Give me way, hey, blow the man down *
* If you give me some
whiskey I'll sing you a song *
* Give me some time
to blow the man down.*
* Give me some time to blow the man down.*
Hello?
你们好哇?
- Hello.
- 你们好
* Come quickly lay aft
To the break of the poop *
* Come quickly lay after
* To me way,hey,blow the man down *
* Or I'll help you along
with the toe of my boot *
* Give me some time
to blow the man down.*
* Give me some time to blow the man down.*
W-W-Wait,what's
going on?
嘿嘿 这是怎么了?
I assume you're referring
to the sea shanty.
我猜你是说这劳动工作歌
It's a rhythmic work song
designed to increase productivity.
这是首用来提高生产力的
节奏感强的劳动歌
Yeah,it's crazy,but it totally works.
是啊 傻了吧唧 但的确有用
Look,we made this Penny
Blossom in under three minutes.
瞧 不到3分钟就做好一个"Penny小花"
Terrific,but that kind of raises
more questions than it answers.
真棒 不过我们的疑问倒是更多了
Penny's making hair accessories.
Penny在做头饰
I'm helping her optimize
her manufacturing process.
我帮她完善她的制作工艺
All right,break's over.
好了 休息结束
* Pay attention to orders
now you one and all...*
Hold on. What are you
using as a bonding agent?
等等 你用什么粘的?
- Hot glue.
- You're kidding.
- 热粘接剂
- 傻了吧你
Any of the cyanoacrylates
would do a better job.
随便一种氰基丙烯酸盐粘合剂
粘的效果都会更好啊
It won't work,the flower's too porous.
不行的 花的孔太多了
What if we infused the bottom layer with
silicone-RTV to provide a better mounting surface?
要是在底层那片注入硅橡胶
打好一个基础面呢?
Intriguing.
有点意思
Good question. ****tion channels?
问的好 你的市场销售渠道呢?
Well,there are the waitresses at my
work,and this cute,little shop in Old Town...
有我上班那的服务生们
还有奥德城的一家小店...
Hush,hush,hush,hush,hush--
virtually non-existent.
嘘嘘嘘 事实上 没有
I'm thinking that we set her up with a
hosted turnkey e-commerce system to start.
我在考虑我们让她从
全权负责的电子商务做起
Why not eliminate the middle man?
何不省去中间人呢?
We couldnstall a small server farm
with a static IP in her bedroom.
我们可以用她卧室的静止IP
装一个服务器场
She'd need some kind of
industrial cooling system.
她得要工业冷却系统
Of course,but before we set up a
marketing and distribution infrastructure,
当然 但建立销售和分销基础设施前
we should finish optimizing
the manufacturing process.
我们得先完善好制作工艺
To start with,she has a terrible problem
with moisture-induced glitter clump.
首先 遇湿凝结的亮片是个老大难
Yeah,it's a bitch.
是啊 烦透了
Uh,I've seen this before.
哦 我见过
Where?
在哪?
It's a common stripper probl.
常见的脱衣舞女问题
They dance,they sweat,they clump.
她们跳啊 流汗啊 凝到一起
Are you thinking about adding a
desiccant like calcium sulfate?
你在想加入些除湿剂
比如说硫酸钙?
Actually,I'm thinking about
this one stripper named Vega.
事实上 我在想那叫Vega的脱衣舞女郎
But sure,calcium sulfate uld work.
但当然 硫酸钙应该行
Let's think out of the box for a moment.
咱跳出框框想一想
How about a molecular sieve?
分子筛怎么样?
I've got a spaghetti
strainer in the kitchen.
我厨房有个意面滤网
Hey,we could liberate some
micro-porous charcoal from the chem lab.
我们可以从化学实验室弄点微孔木炭
Oh,great. Raj,why don't you
and Howard go get the charcoal?
哦 太好了 Raj 你和Howard去拿木炭吧
Leonard,why don't you start working
on some preliminary Web site designs.
Leonard 你着手做网站的初步设计
I'll make some space in our apartment
so we can move the manufacturing process.
我去我们公寓腾点地方
好弄到那边去制作
Well,what's wrong with my apartment?
我的公寓怎么了?
It's not my apartment.
因为不是我的公寓
Wait,wait,what am I going to do?
等下啊 我干点啥呢?
Uh,hey,it's your business.
Do whatever you want.
嘿 是你的事嘛 想干啥干啥吧
Okay,cool.
好吧
I'm going to take a nap.
我睡一小觉去
I'm still tweaking things a little bit,but this
will give you the general idea of the Web site.
我还在不断改进 不过现在
也能看到网站的基本概念
So,what do you guys think?
怎么样?
Uh,pretty much any way I say that
is going to hurt his feelings.
呃...不管咋说都会伤感情的
Okay,what's wrong with it?
好吧 不足在哪里?
- What's wrong with it?
- Not you. I wasn't asking you.
- 不足在哪里?
- 你别说话 没问你
Penny?
Uh,well,it's a little juvenile.
好吧 有点装嫩
I mean,it kind of looks like the
MySpace page of a 13-year-old girl.
我是说 感觉是13岁小姑娘的MySpace页面
No,it doesn't.
没有啊
Please. Dateline could use
it to attract predators.
得了吧 可以用日期栏吊禽兽上钩
Penny,this is your enterprise,so
it's ultimately your decision,
Penny 这是你的生意
你有最终决定权
but based on the quality of his work,I'd
strongly recommend that we let Leonard go.
但鉴于Leonard的工作质量
我强烈建议把他打发掉
You want to fire me?
你想开了我?
What I want is irrelevant.
This is Penny's decision.
我想怎样没关系 是Penny的决定
Penny?
Excuse me,but if I did such a bad job
then why do we already have orders?
抱歉 要是我真做的那么糟
怎么会有订单了呢?
- We do?
- Look.
- 有了?
- 瞧
Mrs. Fiona Fondell from
Huntsville,Alabama has ordered two.
阿拉巴马Huntsville的Fiona Fondell女士
下了两个订单
No kidding. Two?
真的啊 两个?
Look at the comments.
看看评论吧
"Thank you,Penny Blossoms. These will
be perfect to cover my bald spot."
"谢谢 Penny小花 刚好可以
盖住我谢顶的地方"
that... that is so sweet.
真是...真是贴心啊
Camouflaging bald spots.
遮盖谢顶
That's primarily a male concern.
男士一大隐患啊
Perhaps we could expand our market.
可以以此拓宽市场
How are flower barrettes
going to appeal to men?
男的怎么会对花发夹感兴趣的?
We add Bluetooth!
加上蓝牙!
Brilliant. Men love Bluetooth.
聪明 男人喜欢蓝牙
Wait a minute,wait a minute,you want
to make a hair barrette with Bluetooth?
等等 用蓝牙做发夹?
Penny,everything is
better with Bluetooth.
Penny 有了蓝牙事半功倍
Holy crap. Someone just ordered
a thousand Penny Blossoms.
天呐 刚有人定了1千朵的Penny小花
Get out!
不可能
Who needs a thousand sparkly
flower barrettes with rhinestones?
谁会要一千个莱茵仿钻花发夹啊?
"The Fifth Annual East Rutherford,New
Jersey,Gay,Lesbian,Bisexual and Transgender Alliance Luau."
"新泽西东卢瑟福男同 女同
双性恋 变性人联盟5周年庆"
Oh,another market to expand
into-- balding gay men.
哦~我们还以发展一下谢顶同志
And I'll bet lesbians love Bluetooth.
我打赌拉拉肯定也喜欢蓝牙
We should get to work.
开工啦
Wait,wait,why does
it say "one-day rush"?
等等 为什么说是"一天交货"
Since when do we offer a one-day rush?
我们什么时候有这服务了?
Amazon offers one-day rush.
亚马逊就有"一天交货"
Yeah,but they don't have
to glue the books together.
是啊 但是他们不需要把书粘起来
How the hell are we going to make a
thousand Penny Blossoms in one day?
我们到底要怎样才能
在一天内做出一千个?
Don't yell at me. I'm not
manufacturing. I'm just Web design.
别对我吼 我又不是搞生产的
我只是设计网站而已啦
Okay,well,I'm gonna have to
call them and cancel the order.
好 那我打电话告诉他们取消订单
Excuse me,but was this not your goal?
等等 难道这不是你的目标?
Financial independence through
entrepreneurial brilliance and innovation?
通过才智和创新的商业头脑来财政独立
My brilliance and
innovation,of course,but still.
我的才智和创新 当然
I just don't see how
we can pull this off.
我只是不知道要怎么完成订单
That,right there,that equivocation and
self-doubt,that is not the American spirit.
别 你这模棱两可和自我怀疑
可不符合美国精神
Did Davy Crockett quit at the Alamo?
大卫・克劳克拉从阿拉莫之围中退却了吗?
Did Jim Bowie?
吉姆・鲍伊有吗?
They didn't quit. They were massacred...
没 但他们被屠杀了
by like a gazillion angry Mexicans.
被无数墨西哥暴民给屠杀了
Let me put it this way.
这么说吧
Your gross receipts on this one order
will be over $3,000 for one night's work.
你这一夜收入总额可以超过3000美金
You guys get started.
你们快开工
- What are you doing?
- Going online to buy shoes!
- 那你干嘛?
- 我要上网买鞋!
She'll be coming round
the mountain when she comes
* She'll be coming round
the mountain when she comes *
She'll be coming round
the mountain when she comes
* She'll be coming round
the mountain when she comes *
She'll be coming round the mountain
She'll be coming round the mountain...
* She'll be coming round the mountain *
You know,if I wanted to spend my Saturday
nights doing this,I could have stayed in India.
早知道我要在周六晚上做这个
我还不如待在印度
Oh,stop with the fake third world crap.
少装可怜 瞎掰你那第三世界国家生活
Your father's a gynecologist. And
you had a house full of servants.
你爸是妇科医生 你有一屋子仆人
We only had four servants.
我们只有4个仆人
And two of them were children.
其中2个还是未成年
How we doing?
我们干的怎么样了
We have 128 assorted Penny
Blossoms ready to ship.
已经有128朵Penny小花可以发货了
Oh,God,we're never gonna finish in time.
上帝 我们不可能做得完的
Who made Sheldon the boss anyway?
谁提议让Sheldon当头的?
I believe I'm hearing some
negativity on the factory floor.
有人在工厂里散布消极言论
So?
所以呢?
Penny,the labor force is a living
organism that must be carefully nurtured.
Penny 打工仔团体是需要好好教育的
Any counterproductive grumbling must be
skillfully headed off by management. Observe.
任何会产生不良后果的抱怨
必须及时喝止 看着
Less talk,more work!
少说话 多干活
- Nicely done.
- Thank you.
- 做的好
- 谢谢
You hear any union talk,you let me know.
你要看到什么交头接耳 告诉我
* Someone's in the
kitchen with Dinah...*
kitchen I know-ow-ow-ow *
* Someone's in the
kitchen with Dinah...*
Sheldon? Sheldon!
'Cause I sold my soul
to the company store.
* 'Cause I sold my soul
to the company store. *
Honey,do you want some coffee?
要不要来点咖啡?
I don't drink coffee.
我不喝咖啡
Come on,but if you don't stay
awake we'll never finish in time.
行了 你要是睡过去了
我们肯定完成不了
I'm sorry,coffee's out of the question.
对不起 但是我绝不喝咖啡
When I moved to California,I promised my
mother that I wouldn't start doing drugs.
当我搬来加利福尼亚
我答应妈妈不磕药的
Leonard,help.
Leonard 帮帮忙
Sheldon,we still have 380
of these things to make.
Sheldon 我们还有380个要做呢
I have complete faith that
you will make them. Good night.
晚安 你们行的 我对你们绝对有信心
Leonard?
But,Sheldon,without your insight and leadership
this entire enterprise will surely fail.
但是 Shelon 没了你英明的领导
我们的事业绝对是做不起来的
You're right,of course.
当然 你说的对
Here,this will help.
来 这个会有帮助
Very well,but if this leads
to opiates or hallucinogenics,
好吧 但要这让我上瘾或产生幻觉
you're going to have
to answer to my mother.
你得去和我妈交待了
Look at Planck's Constant.
People say it's arbitrary.
说到普朗克常数 有人说不确定
It could not be less arbitrary.
怎么可能呢
If it varied slightly,life as
we know it would not exist. Bam!
如果它稍有改变
我们所知的世界将不复存在 嘣!
Now,now,let's reconsider the entire argument,but
with entropy reversed and effect preceding cause.
现在 让我们考虑熵的改变
和因果联系 重新来看这论点
So you are thinking of a universe
that's not expanding from the center--
你想到的是不由中心扩张的宇宙
no,it is retreating from
a,from a possibility space. Bam!
对的 而是从可能性空间衰减 嘣!
This is a space where we are all
essentially Alice through the looking glass,
在那个空间 我们就像爱丽丝梦游仙境
standing in front the Red Queen,and we're
being offered a cracker to quench our thirst.
穿过镜子站到红心皇后面前
被给予饼干来充饥
Bam!
嘣!
Of course,in another universe,let's
call it universe prime,
当然 在另外一个宇宙
让我们暂时称之为超宇宙
there's another Sheldon,let's
call him Sheldon prime...
那个宇宙也有个Sheldon
让我们称为超Sheldon
- We should have let him go to bed.
- Bam.
- 真该让他睡觉去
- 嘣!
I can't believe we actually did it.
难以置信 我们居然完成了
1,000 friggin' Penny Blossoms.
奶奶的1000朵Penny小花
I just want you guys to know I
am really grateful for your help.
真是太谢谢你们的帮助了
And for ever dollar I make,I'm
going to give you 20 cents.
每挣一块钱我分20分给你们
That's your entire profit margin.
那是你所有的利润了
Then never mind.
哦 那算了
I'll print out the shippi label.
我打印发货标签
What?
等等?
We got an e-mail from the East Rutherford,New
Jersey,Gay,Lesbian,Bisexual and Transgender Alliance.
新泽西东卢瑟福男同 女同
双性恋 变性人联盟又来了封邮件
They want another
thousand Penny Blossoms.
他们再要1000朵Penny小花
Really?
真的?
One-day rush.
一天交货
I really need to take
that off the Web site.
我真得把这选项改了去
d better get started.
我们最好现在开工
You can't be serious.
你开玩笑吧
Come on. What about the living organism
of the workforce and the American spirit?
我们可是有美国精神的职工团体
And Jiminy Crockett at the Alamo?
还有阿拉莫之围里的占美尼?
Davy Crockett. Jiminy
Crockett was a cricket.
是大卫・克劳克拉
占美尼是匹诺曹里的蟋蟀啦
Yes,yes,I know that,okay?
行啦 行啦 我知道?
I'm tired-- I've had
like 18 cups of coffee.
我累了 我已经喝了18杯咖啡了
The point is,if we just
pull together,we can do this.
关键是 我们齐心协力 一定行的
Who's with me?
谁支持我?
Penny,although you may find it
hard to believe,we do have lives.
Penny 虽然你可能很难相信
但是我们都有自己的生活
Leonard?
Sorry.
对不起
My apologies to the gay community
of East Rutherford,New Jersey.
新泽西东卢瑟福同性联盟 我实在抱歉
Zoom,zoom,zoom!
咻 咻 咻!
Where's the coffee?
咖啡呢?
We're all out.
都喝光了
No problem.
没问题
I'll be back before this
banana hits the ground.
我会在香蕉落地前回来
Zoom,zoom,zoom,zoom!
咻 咻 咻 咻!
Yes!
耶!
Sorry,guys,but Secret Agent Laser
Obstacle Lunch is just stupid.
对不起 伙计们
但激光障碍午餐特工真的很傻